Étienne Geoffroy Saint Hillaire Collection 1811-1840 Mss.B.G287p
American Philosophical Society
- Correspondence and notes, 1811-1844; 0.5 linear feet
  - Letter to Frnaçois Laplace?, n.d.; 3p.; Geoffroy Saint-Hilaire, Etienne, 1772-1844 (Box 2)
    1977-744ms
  - Letter to M. Pariset, n.d.; 4p.; Geoffroy Saint-Hilaire, Etienne, 1772-1844 (Box 2)
    1989-1153ms
  - Case of monstrosity by inclusion in a bitch, n.d.; 11p.; Reid, John (Box 2)
- Lectures on the Natural History of Egypt, n.d.; 1 vol., 98p.; Geoffroy Saint-Hilaire, Etienne, 1772-1844
- Notes on Natural History of Egypt, 1825-1829; 1 vol., 36p.; Geoffroy Saint-Hilaire, Etienne, 1772-1844